{
    "id": "bebe2770c3ed401eb2babaf4e526edfc",
    "title": "Subject Verb Agreement Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "One of my friends ..................... .. gone to France.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fab683d71d8741e894b3538214119cc7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Each of the boys ..................... . given a present.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c85e9cd59ea647259f305f72bdea9ddc"
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither of the contestants ..................... .. able to win a decisive victory.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "68ec5b8a3e8a4dbdab1c8176e72fe1d7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Oil and water ..................... .. not mix.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "does",
                "do"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e80ea44ab46a4e61ad00ed241da7a949"
        },
        {
            "question": "He and I ..................... .. at Oxford together.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2943f9d9f9354c209c5b59ea04af6e03"
        },
        {
            "question": "Slow and steady ....................... the race.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "win",
                "wins"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ce897ef97c504de888505290921c04ad"
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither Peter nor James ....................... any right to the property.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "67c6447f231448afa403621d5e59c293"
        },
        {
            "question": "No prize or medal ………………….. given to the boy, though he stood first in the examination.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b05eeb65dc54448c954c1f5a9fadafe6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Either Mary or Alice ..................... responsible for this.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "60104f788702418e929a1d672f0f0d96"
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither the Minister nor his colleagues .....................…… given any explanation for this.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fb30666a37c745caacc78456c552551e"
        }
    ]
}